<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Trust In Heart Demo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tapToBegin">Tap To Begin the Demo!</string>
    <string name="gameBy">A Game Demo By Aaron Turner</string>
    <string name="year">2014, 2015</string>
    <string name="noComply">No Comply Games</string>
    <string name="quit">Quit</string>
    <string name="continueText">Continue</string>
    <string name="newChar">New</string>
    <string name="deleteChar">Delete</string>
    <string name="deleteConfirm">Are you sure you would like to delete this character?
        This action can NOT be undone.</string>
    <string name="editChar">Edit</string>
    <string name="welcomeRRPPGG">A Hero\'s Quest Begins</string>
    <string name="editTextHint">Enter Save File Name</string>
    <string name="editFile">Please enter a name for the character file below</string>
    <string name="importChar">Import</string>
     <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="shop">Shops</string>
    <string name="character">Character</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="title_activity_battle">Battle</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="fight">Fight</string>
    <string name="defend">Defend</string>
    <string name="items">Items</string>
    <string name="run">Run</string>
    <string name="title_activity_creator">Character Creator</string>
    <string name="nameQuestion">What\'s your name?</string>
    <string name="genderQuestion">Are you a boy or girl?</string>
    <string name="skinQuestion">How would you describe your skin tone?</string>
    <string name="dude">Boy</string>
    <string name="lady">Girl</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="tan">Tan</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="statQuestion">Choose a class:</string>
    <string name="tank">Tank - Known for being able to take a lot of damage. They specialize in hit points.
         They are represented by wearing the color green.
        Their special move is "Block", allowing them to cancel enemy damage for a turn. However, it can only be used
        once per battle.</string>
    <string name="warrior">Warrior - Known for being able to deal a lot of damage. They specialize in strength.
         They are represented by wearing the color yellow.
        Their special move is "Charge", allowing them to charge up an attack for a two turns, and get a critical hit
        on their third</string>
    <string name="mage">Mage - Known for being able to use magic. They specialize in intelligence.
         They are represented by wearing the color blue.
        Their special move is "Magic", allowing them to use the magic bounded to their weapons</string>
    <string name="rogue">Rogue - Known for being able to land critical hits and dodge enemy attacks often.
         They are represented by wearing the color grey.
        They specialize in dexterity. Their special move is "Counter", allowing them to reduce damage by the
        enemy and themselves by half. </string>
    <string name="finish">The person above this text is who you will be, save yourself before you delete yourself!</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="reset">Restart</string>
    <string name="crit">It\'s a critical hit!\n</string>
    <string name="ecrit">The enemy attack was critical!\n</string>
    <string name="dodge">You dodged the hit!\n</string>
    <string name="edodge">Your attack has been dodged!\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_char_edit">Character</string>
    <string name="equipment">Equipment</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="totalStats">Total Stats</string>
    <string name="minus">-</string>
    <string name="plus">+</string>
    <string name="viewItems">Items</string>
    <string name="changeEquip">Equipment</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="journal">Journal</string>
     <string name="herosjournal">Trust In Heart</string>
    <string name="title_activity_overworld">Overworld</string>
    
    <string name="itemshop">HP Girl</string>
    <string name="HPshop">Tank Y Moi</string>
    <string name="strshop">Swords Of The Down</string>
    <string name="intshop">MGMP</string>
    <string name="dexshop">Rogue Mind Tricks</string>
     <string name="equip">Equip</string>
    <string name="buy">Buy</string>
    <string name="sell">Sell</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
     <string name="special">Special</string>
    <string name="shopConfirm">Are you sure you would like to buy</string>
    <string name="shopBuy">Thank you for shopping with us!</string>
    <string name="shopEquip">Would you like to equip this item now?</string>
    <string name="shopSell">Would you like to sell your old</string>
    <string name="shopSure">Are you sure?</string>
     <string name="shopCantSell">You cannot sell an item you have equipped!</string>
    <string name="shopFor">for</string>
     <string name="shopNo">It\'s fine! Please, take your time!</string>
    <string name="sold">Sold!</string>
    <string name="equipped">(Equipped)</string>
    <string name="cantEquip">You cannot equip something that is already equipped!</string>
    <string name="itemEquip">You cannot equip an item!</string>
    <string name="equipConfirm">It was successfully equipped!</string>
     <string name="selectChar">Choose Your Character</string>
      <string name="importCharTitle">Import Character</string>
     <string name="fileFormat">Trust In Heart save files must follow this format: "Trust In Heart-(Name).sav"</string>
    
    <string name="entry1">\nEntry #1\n</string>
    <string name="entry2">\nEntry #2\n</string>
    <string name="entry3">\nEntry #3\n</string>
    
    
        
    <!-- Strings for entering shops -->
    
   <string name="store1">Welcome! We don\'t discriminate to any class, as long as you have the required
       skills, you can buy anything you\'d like!</string>
   <string name="store2">Hello! You know a mage\'s magic spell has base damage, but the spell grows stronger
       with intelligence, no matter the base damage!</string>
   <string name="store3">Hi! I just received a note from the head programmer, he says "Thank you for playing
       Trust In Heart!" And he wishes you a nice day!</string>
   <string name="store4">Howdy! Dexterity is a lot more important than it seems!
       Dexterity determines you chances of running, dodging, and even critical hits!</string>
   <string name="store5">Sup! We shop keepers like to play games like everyone else! Lately, I\'ve been
       playing a lot of indie games...</string>
   <string name="store6">Hiya! The shops have been low on customers lately, if you like this game, I\'d appreciate it if
       you would tell your friends! It\'ll help out the shopkeepers and the developer! </string>
   <string name="store7">Hiya! The shops have been low on customers lately, if you like this game, I\'d appreciate it if
       you would tell your friends! It\'ll help out the shopkeepers and the developer!</string>
   <string name="store8">Hiya! The shops have been low on customers lately, if you like this game, I\'d appreciate it if
       you would tell your friends! It\'ll help out the shopkeepers and the developer!</string>
   <string name="store9">Hiya! The shops have been low on customers lately, if you like this game, I\'d appreciate it if
       you would tell your friends! It\'ll help out the shopkeepers and the developer!</string>
   <string name="store10">Hello there! I heard the journal you\'ve been carrying around is a really good read.
       You heroes have the most interesting stories. You should check it out from the main menu!</string>
	<string name="store11">Good Afternoon/Evening/Morning! I don\'t get out of the shop much, I don\'t even know
	    what time it is. But hey, I\'ve always liked working hero\'s retail! </string>
	<string name="store12">Aloha! You know, It\'s not just me working the store, I\'m just part of a big family of twins...
	    Kind of like a nurse and a police officer I heard about. But, Those might just be rumors... </string>
	<string name="store13">Hey There! What does Trust In Heart even mean? All the kids are talking about it these days. Anyways, 
	    why don\t you browse my wares? </string>
	<string name="store14">Hello! Do you hear that music in the background? I think it\'s the kids down the
	    block with their music about chips...</string>
	<string name="store15">ERROR COULD NOT FIND @STRING/WITTYSHOPSAYING </string>
	<string name="store16">Welcome into my store! Have you ever felt like leaving the hero\'s life
	    for a skateboard and broken bones? Yeah, me neither...</string>
	<string name="store17">Yo! You know we store owners used to be in a group called "X-Pressive Arts"?
	    We were all the rage back in the days!</string>
	<string name="store18">What\'s up? The other day a group of guys came in asking about some abulm by
	    some band. It had something to do with Trojans and acts in a play...</string>
	<string name="store19">Howdy! Before you ask... No, we do not sell fuzzy pickles...</string>   
	 <string name="store20">Hi! You know back in my day, our healing items were the active ingredient.
	     And we would get much more health compared to the watered down stuff you heroes have today...</string>  
	 <string name="store21">Hiya! I asked this guy if he liked RPGs the other day. He didn\'t respond the way
	     I had hoped... People and their shooting games... </string>
	 <string name="store22">Hello there! Welcome to the Super Hyper Shop EX Ultra! And, we happen to be
	     the special arcade edition!</string> 
	<string name="store23">Salutations! You ever noticed your score goes down when you buy, and it goes up
	    when you sell? It\'s because your score is determined by guaps, level, wins, and losses!</string> 
	<string name="store24">Hello valued customer! Would you like to pre-order anything with your 
	    purchase today?</string> 
	<string name="store25">Hello! Each skill is unique and has a lot of good benefits, You do not have to 
	    follow your primary class skill, be adventurous!</string>
	<string name="store26">Hiya! You know, since us shop keepers aren\'t held down by the man, we can say whatever we want!
	    For example, "I LOVE PIZZA!". Ha! Take that programming!</string> 
	<string name="store27">Hello valued customer! Would you like to pre-order anything with your 
	    purchase today?</string> 
	<string name="store28">Oh no! I just realized my mom will be home before the mud dries! 
	    Can we make this quick?</string> 
	<string name="store29">Welcome to the store! Where helping heroes is our number two priority! You don\'t
	    want to know what our number one is...</string> 
	<string name="store30">Yo! Out here we only have two real wars... The one with those ugly monsters, and
	    the one about which console is better. And one of them we can actually win... </string> 
	<string name="store31">Hey There! Don\'t be afraid to experiment with other skills other than your primary
	    one. We shop keepers encourage it! </string>
	<string name="store32">Hello! Each skill is unique and has a lot of good benefits, You do not have to 
	    follow your primary class skill, be adventurous!</string>
	<string name="store33">What\'s Up! Some of the other shopkeepers get lonely when buisiness is slow. You
	    should check out what they have to offer some time!</string>
	<string name="store34">Hiya! Sometimes I wonder how people build a game all by themselves. They must
	    be using some kind of computer magic or something...</string>
	  <string name="store35">Welcome to the store! You know that higher intelligence that you have will give you better
	        prices in the stores? You heroes are so persuasive!</string> 
	  <string name="store36">Welcome to the store! You know that higher intelligence that you have will give you better
	        prices in the stores? You heroes are so persuasive!</string> 
	        
	    
	  <!-- leave spaces in between items for intelligence bartering -->
	  
	  
	<!-- Strings for Baby Items -->
	 <string name="babyHD">Baby Hat (Head) Adds 1 HP to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 0HP</string>
   	<string name="babyTD">Baby Shirt (Torso) Adds 1 HP to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 0HP</string>
   		<string name="babyLD">Baby Pants (Legs) Adds 1 HP to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 0HP</string>
    	<string name="babyFD">Baby Shoes (Feet) Adds 1 HP to your total stats!
   		    \nCost:0 Guaps\nRequirements: 0HP</string>
   	<string name="babyWD">Baby Stick (Weapon) Adds 1 Strength to your total stats! And, It gives mages the spell Small Fireball!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 0HP</string>
   
	
	
	    <!-- Strings for Item Shop -->
	    
	    <string name="item1">Water</string>
	    <string name="item1d">Water (Item) heals 4 HP during Battle!
	        \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: None</string>
	     <string name="item2">Tea</string>
       <string name="item2d">Tea (Item) heals 10 HP during Battle!
           \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: None</string>
	        
       <!-- Strings for HP Shop -->
   		<string name="HP1">Plastic Chest</string>
   		<string name="HP1d">Plastic Chest (Torso) Adds 3 HP to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 15 HP</string>
   		<string name="HP2">Wooden Chest</string>
   		<string name="HP2d">Wooden Chest (Torso) Adds 6 HP to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 25 HP</string>
   		    
   		<!-- Strings for STR Shop -->
    	<string name="str1">Durable Sword</string>
   		<string name="str1d">Durable Sword (Weapon) Adds 3 Strength to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 15 Strength</string>
   		<string name="str2">Strong Lance</string>
   		<string name="str2d">Strong Lance (Weapon) Adds 6 Strength to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 25 Strength</string>
   		    
   		<!-- Strings for INT shop -->
    	<string name="int1">Water Slash Book</string>
   		<string name="int1d">Water Slash (Weapon) is a spell with a base damage of 2!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 15 Intelligence</string>
   		<string name="int2">Good Wand</string>
   		<string name="int2d">Good Wands (Weapon) gives you the spell Minor Healing, and adds 3 to your Strength!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 25 Intelligence</string>
   		    
   		<!-- Strings for Dex shop -->
    	<string name="dex1">Red Bandanna</string>
   		<string name="dex1d">Red Bandanna (Head) adds 3 Dexterity to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 15 Dexterity</string>
   		<string name="dex2">Blue Bandanna</string>
   		<string name="dex2d">Blue Bandanna  (Head) Adds 6 Dexterity to your total stats!
   		    \nCost: Guaps\nRequirements: 25 Dexterirty</string>
   		 
   		<!-- Shop reasons you can't buy stuff -->
   		
   		<string name="HPR">You cannot buy that item! Youre HP is too low!</string>
   		<string name="strR">You cannot buy that item! Youre Strength is too low!</string>
   		<string name="intR">You cannot buy that item! Youre Intelligence is too low!</string>
   		<string name="dexR">You cannot buy that item! Youre Dexterity is too low!</string>
   		<string name="scoreR">You cannot buy that item! Youre Score is too low!</string>
   		<string name="guapsR">Sorry, but you do not have enough guaps to buy that...</string>
   		
   		<!-- Demo End -->
   		
   		<string name="demoEnd">Congratulations!</string>
   		
   		<string name="demoEndText">You have successfully defeated the second boss of Trust In Heart, which brings you to
   		     the end of this
   		    demo. I really hope you enjoyed this game, and I really appreciate you taking the time to play it. This
   		    is my very first game, and I expect to release it for free (with a paid version as well) 
   		    by the end of 2014, if not early 2015 for android and Ouya.
   		     I will defintely be adding 6 more worlds, new items, new equipment, more features, all of the coming soon options, 
   		     and much MUCH more!\n\nYou can follow the development of this game from several places.\n\n
   		      The developer, Aaron Turner, twitter account: @Aviscerall\n
   		      No Comply Games Dev Blog: nocomplygames.tumblr.com\n
   		      Trust In Heart Game Page: trustinheartgame.tumblr.com\n\n
   		      Again, thank you very much for playing through this demo, and I hope you are looking forward to the
   		      full game of Trust In Heart!</string>
   		    
   		
   		<!-- Welcome game text -->
   		
   		<string name="welcomeText">So you\'ve decided to play the demo for Trust In Heart huh? Well, I must say you\'ve made a great choice.
   		    This is a game of blood, sweat, and tears, and everything in between! Well, that is, if there is
   		    anything in between. Anyways, this quest will be harder than most you have faced before. And it\'s dangerous
   		    to go alone, without any tips. So, here are some basics on developing yourself into a fine hero.
   		    \n\nHP - This skill determines your health. The amount of damage you can take before calling
   		    it quits in a battle.\n\n
   		    Strength - This skill determines your physical strength, and determines how much damage you will do 
   		    with the fight button in battle.\n\nIntelligence - This skill determines the amount of damage you will
   		    do with the magic button in battle. However, magic is exclusive to the mage class. And as a bonus, 
   		    intelligence will determine the prices inside of shops. The higher the intelligence, the lower
   		     the price!\n\nDexterity - Last but definitely not least, this skill determines your chances of dodging,
   		      landing critical hits, and running away in battles.\n\nBefore I let you go, I must let you know
   		      many events will happen across your journey, and it will all be recorded in your journal.
   		      And, I would also like to let you
   		      know that your skills are your most important assest, develop yourself wisely, and you can defeat any foe.
   		      Press continue below to begin creation of your character...\n\nP.S this demo may have some bugs 
   		      and a lot of features are missing, please do not judge this demo as a final product, it is merely a first look 
   		      into the game and its mechanics.</string>
   		
   		
    <!-- strings for journal &#8230; is for ellipsess (...)-->
    
    <string name="entry1Text">
        A Quest Begins:
I feel like I’ve fallen asleep, and now I’m in a nightmare.
Or that I’m in a nightmare that I woke up still in.
The legendary hero who protected us all is dead.
And now monsters are free to roam the land once more.
The King of Monsters has escaped his eternal prison.
And my dearly beloved is gone. 
We lived a happy life.
In a happy home.
In a peaceful village.
Where we both lived our happy lives.
She meant the world to me.
As she was always there where I needed her.
She was always by my side.
And one day, I proposed.
 Only to have my love snatched away from me.
I fought as hard as I could.
But I was too weak.
And so was my heart.
And now my love is gone.
I cried the entire night.
As the village laid in ruins.
And now that the sun has risen,
I swear vengeance on everyone who did this to
my village, my wife, and myself.
People have never believed in me.
And I’ve never believed in myself.
But I need a hero.
But the hero is dead.
So I must walk this path.
And become the hero the world needs...
 </string>
		
    <string name="entry2Text">The First Step:
I started my adventure in the plains of my hometown.
I gathered the gear I could find in the ruins of my village.
And people warned me not to go.
They told me I was not strong enough, or I would end up just giving up like I usually do.
They told me they were afraid I would die.
But i was in the moment, and I left anyways.
I went training, preparing for the journey ahead of me.
But then, I found a suspicious monster on the outskirts of town,
and when I approached him he spoke of some sort of plans and disgraced my home. 
I easily defeated him to teach him the lesson and continued onward.
The difficult training I had done gave me strength to my surprise, and
after some investigation and exploration, I fought several monsters, 
continually trying to defeat them, and discovered they were all connected , 
plotting and researching, to destroy my home town? 
This was all part of a bigger plan devised by a monster that was their leader. 
I thought this leader may have my love, so followed them to his lair. And what I saw was amazing. 
It was a monster of awe-striking size, with swords for arms, and deep red eyes. 
He laughed at the thought of me defeating him. And I reasoned that I would not be able to defeat him. 
But the fresh need for vengeance was in my heart, and we fought. Even though I lost some battles, 
this feeling pushed me forward, and I never gave up until I emerged as the winner. 
I was relieved to know that know that he was defeated, the people of my village were now safe. 
But, I was still determined to find my love. I searched the lair, but all I found was a map with a circled location. 
In hopes of it being my love. I destroyed the leaders plans, got my things from my home, and left to this new land.
</string>
		
    <string name="entry3Text">
        Losing:
The map lead to me to a vast and barren desert. 
The heat was unbearable. So I decided to rest to regain some of my energy to fight. 
But this did not help. The first monster I fought, mentioned the heat to me. 
Which only made it more unbearable, and it felt so much stronger. And I was baffled by the monster’s strength, 
it was more powerful than the leader I had fought! However I still won, and I continued to fight. 
Though these battles are starting to take a toll on me. I am feeling weaker, and the monsters could notice as well. 
They kept mocking my strength, as they knew I would not be able to defeat them. Even I knew I could not defeat them. 
And by the time I had reached their boss. I wanted to give up. The worry and pain was building up in my mind. 
And, the boss laughed at me, as he knew I had appeared for my love. He knew I was in no position to take her back. 
But I fought him because my heart still had the feeling to fight. And even though I am weak, 
these experiences are making me stronger. It was a long, and grueling battle. But I eventually defeated him, 
though I was filled with intense pain. As he lay there on the ground, I searched through his things, and found a letter. 
It described a location to where my love was being taken, so I took note of it, and limped away. 
I struggled to limp away, and before I left, I looked at the boss. He turned his head, looked back at me, and said, 
“I can see you want to give up hero. Just do it. Revenge and love are a weak man’s emotion. 
and weak men will never be able to stop evil alone.” I knew in my mind, that I really wanted to give up, 
and simply mourn the loss of my love. But my weakening heart made me carry on.

    </string>
    
    <!-- monster story text -->
    <string name="monster1">Hmm, a villager? From this small town? Ha! I\'ll take you out myself! 
        You won\'t even be a problem to our plans.</string>
    <string name="monster2"> Don\'t try to save your town. It\'s already too late. And if you refuse to run away,
         I\'ll stop you here!</string>
    <string name="monster3">So you think you\'re tough because you took out two small guys? I\'ll show you a real
             monster\'s power!</string>
    <string name="monster4">You defeated the guy before me? Don\'t get excited, the boss is getting ready to destroy
        your town. And, I\'m not letting you even get close to him!</string>
    <string name="monster5">So you have come to foil my plans of destroying this city? 
        I hope you know that I am much stronger than 
        you think! I refuse to let you defeat me hero!</string> 
    <string name="monster6">Welcome to my world! I\'ll stop you from getting any closer to my boss and 
        that person in the cage before this heat does!</string>
    <string name="monster7">The boss says you\'re here for the person we nabbed? You defeated that bonehead,
        but you are losing your energy. Are you sure can defeat me?</string>
    <string name="monster8">I can tell that you are getting weaker! 
        You\’re losing you energy hero! Surrender before I destroy you!</string>
    <string name="monster9">I\'m the toughest monster here in the desert. 
        And you are simply a weak hero! 
        I\'m going to enjoy watching you suffer as we take away that person you are after!</string> 
     <string name="monster10">HAHAHA so the monsters told you we have your friend? 
         I hope you know my power is beyond your imagination!
	And you are much too weak to take her back!
         I\'m stopping you here hero! You can not have your precious friend!</string>
    
    
    

</resources>
